You tricked us, didn't you?
I distinctly remember asking
you to become a magical girl.
I just didn't explain precisely
what would be involved.
Why didn't you tell us?!
You never asked.
It wouldn't have bothered you
one bit if you'd never found out.
Mami, for example, never did.
Besides, you humans don't even
realize you have souls in the first place.
Your body's nothing more than a collection of neurons and a centralized cardiovascular system.
In addition, when the human body
ceases to function, the soul is lost.
I gave your soul a physical form to prevent that from happening—
a form you can pick up and
protect with your own hands.
That way, you can battle
witches with greater safety.
Nobody asked you to do that!
You still don't understand what it's like to fight, do you?
For example, take the pain you would
experience upon being impaled by a spear.
This is how it would actually feel.
A single strike would be
enough to incapacitate you.
Pain inhibition was the only reason you
remained standing to the end against Kyouko.
It was only possible because your consciousness isn't directly linked with your body.
That's how you were
able to survive that battle.
In time, you can even learn
to completely cut off pain.
But I wouldn't recommend that,
since it tends to slow you down.
Why...
Why did you do this to us?
You had a wish important enough to commit yourself to a life of battle, did you not?
And your wish came true, didn't it?
I'll never forget the promises we exchanged
I still see it when I close my eyes
I'll move forward as I cast off
this darkness engulfing me
How long will it be before
I see that lost future again?
I'll walk upon this Earth,
and pierce this shadowy veil of unease,
as many times as necessary
The clock that's endlessly ticked away
now tells of the beginning
Let's open the once-closed door,
with these unwavering feelings
My heart started racing once again to paint the future
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me
So I won't be afraid
No matter what happens next, I won't give in
Can you accept your true feelings?
Episode 7
Stand.
Bow.
Homura, did you know about that?
Why didn't you tell us?
Nobody I've warned has
ever believed me before.
Why would Kyubey
do something so cruel?
He doesn't think it's cruel.
He's a creature that doesn't
understand human values.
He'd just say it was an appropriate
payment for bringing about a miracle.
That's not fair at all!
How could he do that to her?
All Sayaka wanted was to heal the person she loved!
It was still a miracle.
He made the impossible possible.
Even if Miki Sayaka dedicated her entire life to caring for him,
he would never have recovered
enough to play the violin again.
Normally a miracle costs
far more than a human life,
but that's the price for
which Kyubey sells them.
Sayaka won't be able to go back to her normal life?
I've said this before, have I not?
Give up on Miki Sayaka.
Sayaka saved me!
If she hadn't been a magical girl at the time,
Hitomi and I would have died!
Don't confuse gratitude with responsibility.
There is no way for you to save her.
If you're thinking of returning the favor to alleviate your own sense of guilt,
then I suggest you reconsider.
Homura, why are you always so cold?
I suppose it's because I'm
no longer human as well.
How can I visit Kyousuke after being turned into this thing?
How long are you gonna lie there
feeling sorry for yourself, dummy?
Come out for a bit.
We need to talk.
You regret what was done
to your body, don't you?
I'm starting to think it
doesn't really matter.
I mean, I'm able to do what I want because I acquired these powers.
It's not really something I regret.
You just got what you deserved.
Yeah! You can just think of it that way.
If you live only for yourself,
everything you do is your own fault.
You have no reason to resent others,
and you'll never have any regrets.
You can get through just about anything if you think of it that way.
Why did you bring me
all the way out here?
It's kind of a long story.
Want one?
Don't ever waste food.
I'll kill you if you do.
This place was my dad's church.
He was an extremely
honest and kind person.
The type of person who'd cry just
from reading the morning paper
and put serious thought into how
to make the world a better place.
My dad always said that a new
religion was needed to save a new era.
That's why he started preaching things that weren't part of the scripture.
As you'd expect, people stopped coming to his sermons.
Then he got excommunicated by the church.
No one would listen to what he had to say.
It shouldn't have been a surprise.
From the outside, it would've
looked like some sketchy cult.
No matter how right he was,
no matter how logical
the things he said were,
he was just an outcast
in the eyes of society.
Our whole family was left
with nothing, not even food.
I couldn't accept it.
My dad wasn't saying anything wrong.
It was just different from what
people were used to hearing.
If they had just listened to him for five minutes,
it would've been obvious that he was right.
But in the end, no one listened to him.
I couldn't stand it.
It was unforgivable.
I couldn't bear the fact that
no one understood him.
That's why my wish was that everyone would listen to my dad's words.
The next morning, his church
was filled with people.
The number of believers multiplied at a frightening rate each day,
and I became yet another magical girl.
No matter how good his sermons were,
they wouldn't get rid of the witches.
I thought that was where I came in, so
I got all hyped up about it like an idiot,
thinking we'd save the world together—
he from the light and I from the shadows.
But one day my dad found
out what was going on.
He completely lost it when he realized all his followers were only there because of magic.
He called me, his own daughter,
a witch who swayed the hearts of others.
Oh, the irony.
I mean, I was the one who'd been fighting real witches every night.
That ruined my father.
He met a pitiful end.
He started binge drinking,
lost his grip on reality,
and wound up killing
his family, then himself.
Only I was left.
My wish destroyed my entire family.
Because I made a wish for someone else
without knowing what he really wanted,
I ruined many people's lives.
That's when I swore to myself that
I'd never use magic for others again.
I'd use my powers only for myself.
Miracles aren't free.
If you wish for hope, an equal amount of despair is scattered across the world.
It all cancels out to zero. That's how
the balance of the world is maintained.
Why are you telling me this?
You just need to stop worrying and do whatever you want.
Live only for yourself.
That doesn't add up.
If you're only living for yourself,
then why worry about me?
We both started off with the same mistake.
You shouldn't start doing
more things you'll regret.
You've already paid too high
a price for what you got.
So now, you should start thinking about how to get your money's worth.
Like you, huh?
That's right.
I've come to realize my mistake,
but you're still making yours.
I couldn't watch you go on like that.
I had the wrong idea about you.
I'm sorry for that. I really am.
But I don't regret having used my wish for someone else.
I've decided never to regret my actions,
so as not to cheapen the feelings I cherish.
Never again.
Why are you...
I don't believe I paid too high a price.
I can do wonderful things with this power, if I use it right.
And what about you?
How did you get those apples?
Where did you get the
money to pay for them?
You can't tell me, can you?
In that case, I can't eat them.
I wouldn't even want one.
You dumbass!
We're magical girls!
There's no one else like us!
I will continue to fight in my own way.
If that interferes with your life,
you're welcome to try
and kill me again.
I no longer bear you any
ill will, but nor will I lose.
Good morning, Sayaka!
Good morning, Sayaka.
Good morning.
What happened yesterday?
I was just feeling a little unwell.
Sayaka...
It's okay. I'm fine now.
Don't worry about me.
Anyway, let's get...
My, has Kamijou been
released from the hospital?
Kamijou, are you okay
to come to school?
Yeah. It wouldn't be rehab if I was
cooped up in my home all day.
My goal is to walk without
crutches by next week.
I'm glad Kamijou's doing well.
Yeah...
Sayaka, go say hi.
You haven't said anything
to him yet, right?
I'm... okay for now.
So, what did you want to talk about?
I need some relationship advice.
I've been keeping something from you and Madoka for a while now.
Huh?
O-Okay...
I've...
been attracted to Kamijou Kyousuke for some time now.
I-I see.
I never would've expected
that from you, Hitomi.
Kyousuke sure is a lucky guy—
You've known him for a long time, haven't you?
Yeah, but we're just old acquaintances, I guess.
Is that really all?
I've decided that I won't lie to myself anymore.
What about you?
Sayaka, can you accept your true feelings?
Wh-What are you talking about?
You're a precious friend to me.
So I don't want to steal him from you or try to court him behind your back.
You've spent far more time with him than I have.
That's why you should have the right to go after him first.
Hitomi...
I will confess my love to Kamijou after school tomorrow.
You have one whole day.
Please decide on a course of
action that you won't regret.
Decide whether or not you'll
tell him how you feel.
I-I...
Madoka...
Can I come with you?
I don't want you to be all on your own.
Why are you...
Why are you so kind to me?
I don't deserve it.
That's not true.
Today, I almost regretted what I'd done.
For just a moment, I wondered what would have happened if I hadn't saved Hitomi.
Some hero I turned out to be.
Mami would be ashamed to have known me.
I'm going to lose Kyousuke to Hitomi!
And there's nothing I can do about it!
I'm already dead!
I'm a zombie!
How can I ask him to hold this dead body?
How can I ask him to kiss my cold lips?
Thank you. I'm sorry.
Sayaka...
I'm fine now.
I feel better.
Anyway, let's go. Those witches aren't gonna slay themselves.
Right.
I'm surprised you're
just sitting here watching.
She's fighting a witch
today, not a familiar.
It'll drop a Grief Seed.
It's not a pointless hunt.
And you'd let her take
your prey for that, huh?
Damn, that idiot.
She's having trouble.
Sayaka!
Goddamnit. I couldn't
just sit there any longer.
Just stay back for now.
I'll show you how it's done.
Hey!
Don't get in my way.
I can do it myself.
Sayaka!
Don't tell me you...
It's true!
If I just detach myself...
it doesn't hurt at all!
Stop... Please stop...
One day the light of love burning in your eyes
will transcend time
and destroy one of this world's dreams
as it spirals toward the apocalypse
What is it that you seek
now that you're done hesitating?
Is there a glimpse of hope for tomorrow
beyond this greedy admiration?
I want to be armed with the power
to shatter even the darkness in my hand,
just like the ancient magic in my childhood dreams,
the next time I see your innocent smile.
In my trembling hands I hold
the courage of a plucked flower
My feelings are all I can rely on;
the prayer that awakens
the light
Illustrated by   Takashi Tensugi
I won't be like the rest of you magical girls.
That's what I've decided.
I don't need any reward for my work.
I'll never use magic for my own benefit.
I really was an idiot
Episode 8
I really was an idiot.